=================================
 THE POWER AND GIFT OF CURIOSITY
=================================

   “The best thing for being sad," replied Merlin, beginning to puff and blow, "is to learn something. 
That's the only thing that never fails. You may grow old and trembling in your anatomies, you may 
lie awake at night listening to the disorder of your veins, you may miss your only love, you may 
see the world about you devastated by evil lunatics, or know your honour trampled in the sewers 
of baser minds."

   "There is only one thing for it then — to learn. Learn why the world wags and what wags it.
That is the only thing which the mind can never exhaust, never alienate, never be tortured by, 
never fear or distrust, and never dream of regretting. Learning is the only thing for you. 
Look what a lot of things there are to learn!” 

   ☼ T.H. White, The Once and Future King



“The important thing is not to stop questioning. Curiosity has its own reason for existing.” 

   ☼ Albert Einstein



“Around here, however, we don't look backwards for very long. We keep moving forward, 
opening up new doors and doing new things, because we're curious...and curiosity keeps 
leading us down new paths.” 

   ☼ Walt Disney Company